

Renata Apostolova

Software tester

As part of the occasional bug bushing in my experience in the IT industry, I realized that QA should be something I could do fulltime. I am currently on the lookout for a starting QA position in order to begin the quest of professional bug-hunting.

renata.karamicheva@gmail.com

Skopje

+38970936888

n linkedin.com/in/renata-apostolova-91727b192

EDUCATION

Software testing academy Brainster

03/2020 - 10/2020 Skopje
Courses / Modules

- Excel - SQL

SCRUM
 Automation testing
 REST API testing
 Manual Testing
 Performance testing
 Defect reporting

PostmanJava

Project Management

Faculty of Electrical engineering and informatics

09/2014 - Present Skopje

Biology professor

Faculty of natural sciences

09/2008 - 06/2012 Skopje

WORK EXPERIENCE

Content uploader

IT-Labs

09/2016 - 06/2019 Skopje

General info

 A career switch, where I entered the IT industry. We managed the content of a client's website using an inhouse developed tool which was part of the admin console of the site itself. Apart from the day to day content management, we double served as beta testers for new version always on the lookout for bugs.

Receptionist

Hotel Vlaho

Skopje

General info

 From room bookings to arrangements with 3rd party suppliers, the job was demanding from both organizational and communication perspective as soft skills are needed to manage the ever-demanding guests.

Biology Teacher

Yahya Kemal

09/2013 - 06/2014

General info

 As a substitute teacher, apart from the usual teaching, I was able to further advance my English since the lessons were only English speaking.

SKILLS

Manual Testing SQL Operating systems (linux)

Microsoft Office REST API testing SCRUM

Automation testing Defect reporting Postman

PROJECTS

Wisdom To Go (08/2019)

- A project done by friends (one developer, one designer). They helped me get a real-life feeling of what software testing is.
- https://wisdomtogo.flycricket.io

Cargodom (06/2020 - 07/2020)

- As part of the Brainster academy we were writing test cases for Cargodom as well as some automated test scenarios.
- https://www.cargodom.com

ADDITIONAL COURSES

Best QA manual software testing

Manual testing processes along with live project test and JIRA examples. https://www.udemy.com/share/1003toBkIZd1tWTX4=/

Software testing

Pragmatic tips about the job and methodologies. https://www.udemy.com/share/101t14BkIZd1tWTX4=/

LANGUAGES

English Greek

Full Professional Proficiency Elementary Proficiency

INTERESTS

Thriller movie Shopping Travel Cooking

Reading